本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
好漢兩個半
第十二季  第四集
翻譯：帥氣誘惑賽太公   可愛誘惑YY貓   阿蘅阿蘅   淚點無限低的大菜
校對：帥氣誘惑賽太公   可愛誘惑YY貓  總監   YY貓
后期：灰灰是菇涼  時間軸：YY貓
波塔  早安
Oh, hey, morning, Berta.
警告一下  男人在干活中
Little warning, man at work.
這里弄弄  那里搞搞
Doing a little banging and screwing.
也警告你一下
Little warning for you.
在酒吧待到凌晨兩點的女人也是"東搞西搞"
Woman at bar until 2:00 A.M. doing the same thing.
你是在干嘛
What are you doing?
給房子裝嬰兒保護裝置
I am baby-proofing the house.
領養機構的要求
It's a requirement of the adoption agency,
而且這也是好事
and it's a good thing, too.
這廚房簡直是殺嬰神器
This here kitchen is a death trap.
這里有一大堆能弄死人的東西
Whole mess of things up in here that can kill someone.
有刀  有火  毒清潔劑  滾燙的沸水
We got knives, we got fire, poison, scalding hot water,
艾倫過期的魚肉卷
Alan's leftover fish tacos.
你緊張過度了
You worry too much.
杰克當年沒少吃到地板蠟跟清潔劑
Jake ate a steady diet of floor wax and detergent,
你看他...
and he turned out...
其實你說的還真有道理
Yeah, maybe it's not a bad idea.
我把所有的柜子跟抽屜都固定了
I locked all the cabinets and the drawers,
爐灶也加上了安全開關
put these safety knobs on the stove,
如果你想要拿出那些化學藥品
and if you want to access any chemicals,
會需要用特殊的磁力鑰匙
you will need a special magnetic key.
對了  你洗衣服的時候
Oh, by the way, when you're doing the laundry,
留意有沒有特殊磁力鑰匙掉出來
keep your eye out for a special magnetic key.
為什么毛巾抽屜也要上鎖
Why would you need to lock the towel drawer?
你的大麻是藏在藥物抽屜里的啊
You hide your pot in the medicine cabinet.
我猜的
I'm guessing.
那不是普通的毛巾抽屜
That is no ordinary towel drawer.
那是災難的起源第一步
That's the first step on the stairway to disaster.
我太醉  懶得聽這些狗屁
Oh, I'm too hungover for this crap.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
你想象一下  小孩拉開這個抽屜
All right, imagine, if you will, child pulls out the drawer,
爬上去到臺面上  在爬過去
climbs up onto the counter and toddles over to the window
到沒鎖的窗邊
that has been left open
沒鎖是因為艾倫覺得蒸花椰菜讓他反胃
because Alan finds the smell of steaming broccoli
所以打開窗透氣
to be "gaggy."
結果呢  小孩看到了美麗的風箏
Whereupon, the child spots a beautiful kite,
很可能是蝴蝶或皮卡丘圖案的
most likely in the shape of a butterfly or a Pikachu.
小孩伸手想抓風箏
The child reaches for the kite,
滾出窗外
tumbles out the window,
掉到雨篷  彈出去  飛在空中
bounces off the awning, flying through the air,
本來馬上要死了
heading toward certain death,
結果奇跡發生
when, miraculously, it is caught
他被光上身的馬修·麥康納接住了
by a shirtless Matthew McConaughey.
"別擔心  你的小孩一切都會很好
"Don't worry, your baby's gonna be all right,
很好  很好"
all right, all right."
知名男演員  在1993年他出演的電影《年少輕狂》中
有著著名的臺詞"all right, all right, all right"
是啊
Yeah, sure.
我們這次是走運  孩子沒事
You know what, we got lucky this time,
但我們不能每次都有馬修·麥康納來救啊
but we can't depend on McConaughey every time.
行啊  但我以后要把你的大麻藏起來了
Okay, I'm gonna have to start hiding the pot from you.
不怕一萬  只怕萬一
Better safe than sorry.
每個樓梯間  每個廁所  每個尖銳角落
Every stairway, every toilet, every sharp corner
都被鎖上  閂上或加墊了
has been locked, latched or padded.
沒人可以在這個家里受傷
No one is getting hurt in this house.
燙
Hot!
燙  燙
Hot! Hot!
很好  很好  很好
All right, all right, all right.
你也看到了
So, as you can see,
我在樓梯口裝了安全門
I installed a gate at the top of the stairs,
樓梯底下也裝了安全門  為了額外小心
at the bottom of the stairs, and as an extra precaution,
我在樓梯中間也裝了一個
I put one in the middle of the stairs.
好還要更好
Overachiever.
我想他只是想關住我  怕我跑掉
I think he's just trying to keep me from getting away.
你的嬰兒防護措施做得很棒
Well, you did a great job baby-proofing.
我想象不到有誰在這家里能受傷
I can't imagine anyone getting hurt in this house.
是嗎  你試試說我穿這牛仔褲顯胖
Really? Try telling me I look fat in these jeans.
夠了  收了你的神通吧  霹靂火
Okay, flame off, Human Torch.
所以下一步是怎么樣呢
So, uh, so, what do we do next?
挺簡單了
Oh, well, it's pretty simple.
我走到外面陽臺等
I walk out onto the deck,
你就把一疊百元大鈔放桌上
you put a pile of hundreds on the table,
我走進來  把錢塞進皮包里
I come back, slip them into my purse,
小孩就是你的了
and you get a kid.
我車庫的工具箱底有5千塊錢
I have $5,000 in the bottom of a toolbox in the garage.
我開玩笑的
I was joking.
我也是
As was I.
我本來不打算在審核完畢前
Anyway, uh, I wasn't gonna say anything
告訴你們倆這消息的
until you guys passed the inspection,
但貌似我們已經找到了
but it looks like we may have found
適合你們兩個的孩子了
a potential match for the two of you.
我們
We're...
我們要有孩子啦
We're getting a baby.
你是說真的嗎  太不敢相信了
Are you serious? This is unbelievable.
別著急  目前還只是在
Well, slow down; all that's happened so far
一名懷孕的媽媽看過你們的資料
is a pregnant mother has seen your profile
很想見見你們
and wants to meet you.
有人看過我的資料還想見我嗎
Somebody saw my profile and wants to meet me?
跟在相親網站上差好多哦
That's so different than the dating sites.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
她是誰  哪里人
Who is she? Where is she from?
她幾歲了  肚子里是男是女
How old is she? Is she having a boy or a girl?
別  別說說說說說
Wait, no, la-la-la-la-la!
我不想知道  我想有驚喜
I don't want to know. I want to be surprised.
沃頓  你想太多了
Walden, you're getting ahead of yourself.
你是說女孩嗎
Did you say girl?
我好像聽到你說是女孩
I thought I heard you say girl.
算了  其實呢
Wait, no, you know what?
根本無所謂
Doesn't matter.
只要手腳健全
Ten fingers and ten toes--
這才是最重要的
that's all that matters.
你不說話是因為是個男孩嗎
Are you not saying anything 'cause it's a boy?
天啊  我們要有兒子啦
Oh, my God, we're having a boy!
沃頓
Okay, Walden,
當你見到孩子生母
when you meet the mother,
你最好看起來是很冷靜  鎮定的父親
you want to come off as a calm, stable father.
不是去參加賈斯丁·比伯演唱會的14歲少女
Not like a 14-year-old girl at a Justin Bieber concert.
抱歉  我們是太興奮了
Sorry, we're just really excited.
沒事  我懂  我也很為你們興奮
No, I get it. I'm excited for you.
等見面時間確定好了  我再通知你們
I'll call you when the meeting is set up.
對了
Oh, and by the way,
我覺得你穿那條牛仔褲  看起來超棒
I think you look fantastic in those jeans.
姑娘  我們絕對會是好閨蜜
Girl, we are gonna be BFFs.
我們要有孩子啦
We're gonna have a baby.
We're gonna have a baby!
我們要有孩子啦
我們得慶祝一下
Oh, we have to celebrate.
我去車庫里面拿點香檳
Uh, I'll go to the garage and get some champagne.
太好了  我們要有孩子啦
Great! We're gonna have a baby!
我們要有...
We're gonna have a...
等等  我們車庫里沒有香檳啊
Wait, we don't have champagne in the garage.
我藏錢的工具箱
My toolbox!
艾倫
Alan!
給
Here.
我買了這個給你
I got this for you.
為啥
Why?
如果我們穿著情侶毛衣
I think it would be nice
去見寶寶的母親  那更有說服力呀
if we wore matching sweaters to meet the birth mom.
情侶裝哦
Twinsies.
我們應該是以已婚夫婦的身份
We're supposed to be a married couple,
而不是理發店四重唱的兩位團員
not half of a barbershop quartet.
不能兩者兼具嗎
Can't we be both?
* 麥克馬丁小姐  賜我一個孩子 *
* Miss McMartin, bring me a kid *
* 跟你結婚  真是一件蠢事*
* Marrying you was a dumb thing I did *
你唱太低了
You were flat.
你說那位母親  會不會很辣
So, the mom-- you think she's hot?
她都懷孕九個月了啊
She's nine months pregnant!
我知道啊
I know.
孕婦誘惑超正點
Love me some preggos.
胸圍38  腰圍62  臀圍38
38-62-38.
寶貝真是有前有后啊
Baby got back and front.
聽著
Okay, listen.
如果想要這女孩把孩子給我們
If we want this girl to give us her baby,
她一定要認為我們是一對合適的人選
she has to think that we're a well-adjusted couple.
如果她感受到你那股猥瑣勁兒
If she gets a creepy vibe off of you,
她肯定會立馬轉身逃跑
she's gonna turn and run the other way.
我之所以這么說
And I'm only saying this
因為我深受你那股猥瑣勁兒毒害
'cause I'm getting a creepy vibe off of you.
你自己上網搜"海倫·米倫露點照"  還好意思說
Says the guy who Googled "Helen Mirren nip slip."
1945年出生  一生得過無數獎的英國女演員
海倫是永恒的女神
Helen is timeless.
聽著  如果你搞砸了
Now, listen. If you mess this up for me,
我一定會讓你生不如死
I will make your life a living hell.
現在記住  我們深愛彼此
Now, remember, we love each other.
你好  媽媽
Hello, Mama.
你們好
Hi.
你就是凱西吧
Hi, you must be Kathy.
歡迎來到我們的馬里布夢想豪宅
Yes, uh, welcome to our Malibu dream house.
他是肯
He's Ken.
那我豈不就是芭比了
Oh, I guess that makes me Barbie.
我是沃頓
I'm Walden.
他是艾倫
This is Alan.
快進來
Come in.
外套給我吧
Here, c-can I take your coat?
謝謝你
Oh, thank you.
瞧瞧你
Look at you!
-孕味十足呀  -掛衣服去
- So very pregnant. - Coat.
我知道
I know.
我從七月開始就沒見過自己的腳
I haven't seen my feet since July.
我鞋子是一對嗎
Am I wearing matching shoes?
貌似還真不是
Actually, no.
但是一點都不突兀  很可愛啊
Uh, but you know what, it works. It's cute.
快請坐
Um, please sit.
對啊  你感覺如何
Yeah, please. How you feeling?
我的膝蓋超腫
My ankles are swollen,
我的背超疼  更別說我的胸部了
my back hurts, and forget about my breasts.
我都沒注意到  因為我是同性戀嘛
I haven't even noticed, you know, 'cause I'm gay.
那是...
That's...
那是我的彩虹勇士
That's my rainbow warrior.
總是在揮舞他的性向旗幟
Always waving his flag.
即使跟任何事無關也要提
Even when it relates to nothing.
聊聊你自己吧
Um, so, uh, tell us about Kathy.
我想你們應該了解我的第一件事是
I think the first thing you should know about me
這個  并不能代表我是什么樣的人
is this is not representative of who I am.
我剛從加州大學洛杉磯分校畢業
See, I just graduated from UCLA.
這孩子是因為春假時去拉斯維加斯懷上的
The baby is a result of a spring break trip to Vegas.
我猜在拉斯維加斯發生的事
Ah. I guess what happens in Vegas
都留在你肚子里了
stays in Kathy.
是啊  我花了六個月的時間才知道
Yep, took me about six weeks to figure out
我每天早上的晨吐
that my morning sickness
不是一場久達六個月的超級宿醉
wasn't just a really bad hangover.
我們都會犯錯誤
Well, we all make mistakes.
某天早上我醒來  就發現自己跟這貨結婚了
One morning, I woke up married to this one.
主要是因為這不在我的五年計劃之內
See, bottom line, this wasn't part of my five-year plan.
我的五年計劃是念法律學校  當法官文員
You know, law school, clerk for a judge,
開始我的事務所
start my own practice.
哇  真是野心勃勃呀
Wow, that's-that's impressive.
艾倫的兒子  杰克
Uh, Alan's son, Jake,
也有一個念完十年級的五年計劃
had a five-year plan for the tenth grade.
瞧  這就是為什么我喜歡你們
See, that's why I liked your profile.
你當過父母
You have parenting experience.
我也喜歡你的幽默感
Your sense of humor came through.
我有點喜歡你們是同性戀了
And I kind of love that you're gay.
肯定不及我們喜歡自己
Not as much as we do.
-對吧  沃沃熊  -對的  艾艾貓
- Right, Wally Bear? - That's right, Alley Cat.
即使我不能參與寶寶的人生
Even though I'm not gonna be part of the baby's life,
但我也想做它唯一的媽咪
I like the idea of being the only mom.
這點我完全能理解
I can totally understand that.
可能是因為我媽媽是個冷漠毒舌的酒鬼
Probably because my mom was an ice-cold, sharp-tongue alcoholic
喜歡整天購物和做美容  不喜歡跟我一起玩
who preferred shopping and spas over spending time with me.
這點我完全能理解
And I can totally understand that.
跟我聊聊你們吧
So, tell me about you.
你們為什么想要組建家庭
What made you guys decide to start a family?
撫養我的兒子
Uh, well, raising my son
是我這輩子最重要的人生經歷
was one of the greatest experiences of my life,
我想沃頓也能擁有這份喜悅
and I just wanted Walden to feel that same joy.
是啊  對我而言有兩個原因
Yeah, I mean, for me it's a couple reasons.
一是我感覺我人生好像缺少點什么
I-I felt like something was missing in my life,
我想要回饋社會
and I wanted to give back,
二是有了孩子  我才能用多人合用車道
and having a kid will allow me to drive in the carpool lane.
高速路上一條只允許兩個人以上乘坐同一輛車使用的車道
能開懷大笑真好
It's nice to laugh again.
不過我剛笑尿了一點在你們的沙發上
Except I just peed a little on your sofa.
我幫你拿東西擦吧
I'll get you something.
其實我手邊正好有東西可以擦
Oh, uh, actually, I got something right here.
寶寶剛踢了我一下
The baby just kicked.
我感覺到了
I felt it.
看來你肚子里住這個足球明星啊
Oh, looks like someone's got a little soccer star in there.
天啊  你味道真好聞
God, you smell good.
艾倫  你想抬起頭呼吸下新鮮空氣嗎
Alan, you want to come up for some air?
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
我太興奮了
Just got excited.
-因為寶寶  -當然
- About the baby. - Sure.
那么凱西
So, uh, Kathy,
你知道肚子里的是男孩還是女孩嗎
uh, do you know if it's a boy or a girl?
我不知道  但你們的檔案寫
I don't, but your profile said
你們沒有性別偏好  不是嗎
you didn't have a gender preference, right?
是的
Oh, that's right.
就像我20多歲時  男女通吃
Just like me in my 20s.
你們倆太好玩了
You guys crack me up.
你們一定會是很棒的爸爸
You're gonna make great dads.
根據我買的馬克杯  應該是世界上最棒的爸爸
Oh, world's greatest, according the coffee mugs I bought.
那就好  因為我已經決定了
Well, that's good, because I made up my mind.
我要你們領養我的孩子
I want you to have my baby.
-不是吧  -是的
- No! - Yes.
天啊  你說的是真心話嗎
Oh, my God! You did not just say that!
你個小賤人
You bitch!
謝謝  凱西
Thank you, Kathy.
謝謝  拉斯維加斯
Thank you, Vegas.
謝謝  破掉的套套
Thank you, broken condom.
你可以謝謝果汁店買一贈一的龍舌蘭酒
Well, you can thank two-for-one tequila shots at the Tropicana.
別忘了肚子里那個小家伙喲
Let's not forget this little guy.
你感受到它動了嗎
Do you feel it moving?
我能感覺到"它"在"變大"
I can feel it growing.
迎嬰聚會最好的禮物
Okay, best shower gift:
巴里  孩子的第一支煙槍
Barry. Baby's first bong.
對
Yep.
和孩子的尿片一樣
And just like the kid's diaper,
里面都是邪惡[惡臭]的綠色東西
it's full of stinky green stuff.
披薩馬上到
The pizza's on its way.
在這個時候  誰想喝點啤酒
In the meantime, uh, who wants a beer?
好啊
Yeah.
開始喝吧
There we go.
沃頓  你會是一個好爸爸
Walden, you are gonna make a great dad.
艾倫  杰克是你養大的
And, Alan, you've already raised Jake,
所以  你就反著來養這個孩子吧
so I guess just... do the opposite.
我仍然不敢相信
I still can't believe it's even possible
兩個男人也能生孩子
for two men to have a baby.
這到底是什么時代啊
What an age we live in.
科學太先進了  對吧
Science, right?
拉里  這孩子不是我們生的
Larry, we're-we're not actually having a baby.
是我們領養的
We're adopting.
放"空槍"哈[無精或弱精癥]
Ah, shooting blanks, huh?
如果艾倫懷孕了
Well, I guess if Alan gets pregnant,
你肯定就知道他偷人了
you'll know he's been cheating on you.
你倆真的結婚了
So you two are really married, huh?
-對啊  -很瘋狂吧
- Yep. - Yeah, crazy, isn't it?
不  我告訴你們什么才是瘋狂
No, I'll tell you what's crazy.
你從來也沒想泡過我  沃頓
You have never hit on me once, Walden.
我們每天一起工作  面對面
I mean, we worked together every day, side by side,
從來沒有長時間的對視過
and not so much as a lingering glance
也沒聽你說過"你今天挺帥  巴里"
or a "Gee, you look nice today, Barry.
"你是不是瘦了  巴里"
"You lost a little weight, Barry?
"這條工裝短褲很顯你的小腿肌肉  巴里"
Those cargo shorts really flatter your calves, Barry."
不是的  老兄
No, man.
我們結婚是為了領養一個孩子
We got married so I could adopt a baby.
我們是假夫妻
That... we're a pretend couple.
就像你"在加拿大的女友"
It's kind of like your "Girlfriend in Canada."
拜托  奧利維亞是真的
Okay, Olivia is real.
好吧  看她發給我的裸照
I mean, just... Okay, look at these nude photos she sent me.
這是詹妮弗·勞倫斯[奧斯卡影后]
That's Jennifer Lawrence.
老是有人說她像
She gets that all the time.
再過幾天  我就是一位父親了
In a couple days, I'm gonna be a dad.
我即將為一個
I'm gonna be completely responsible
毫無自理能力的人
for the emotional and financial well-being
提供感情依托
of someone who is completely incapable
和財產保障
of taking care of themselves.
謝謝你一直扮演"嬰兒"的角色讓我練手
Thank you for being my test baby.
我希望是個男孩
I'd keep my fingers crossed for a boy.
為什么
Why?
很簡單的數學問題
Well, basic math.
如果你有個兒子  你只需要擔心一個雞雞
If you have a boy, you only have to worry about one penis.
如果你有個女兒  你就得擔心所有男人的雞雞
You have a girl, you have to worry about them all.
無論如何  你們都會愛孩子
Either way, you're gonna love it.
當爸爸是世界上最幸福的事情
Being a father is the best thing in the world.
你的孩子多大了
How old are your kids?
我兒子15歲
Well, my son is 15
我的私生女今年滿11歲
and my secret daughter is going to be 11 this year.
你的私生女
Your... your secret daughter?
對  她和我的情婦長得很像
Yeah, she looks a lot like my secret wife.
孩子就是這么神奇
You know, kids are amazing.
你得把所有的知識都傳授給他
You know? You get to pass all this knowledge down
塑造他的思想意識
to this little person and-and shape their mind.
比如  如何向女孩搭訕
Like, you know, how to talk to girls
朋友需要你的時候  如何支持他們
and how to be there for your friends when they need you.
你也可以教他們每回結賬的時候
Oh, you can teach them your ability to always be in the bathroom
總能剛好在廁所的本事
whenever the dinner check comes.
那是本能
That's pure instinct.
教不了的
Can't be taught.
我所有的回憶都跟我爸相關
You know, all my memories revolve around my dad.
他把我的電子寵物扔到垃圾處理機里
The time he threw my Tamagotchi down the garbage disposal.
他和我的舞伴調情
Time he made a pass at my prom date.
他和我媽離婚  娶了我的舞伴
Time he divorced my mom and married my prom date.
各位  各位  是醫院打來的
Guys. Guys, it's the hospital.
如果是我的病人  說我不在
Oh, if it's one of my patients, I'm not here.
別擔心  如果我是你孩子的醫生
Oh, don't worry. If I'm your kid's doctor,
我不會這么做
I won't do that.
都是這么說的
It's what you say.
凱西快生了
Kathy's in labor!
我們得走了
We got to go!
我叫車
I'll get an Uber.
我去拿兒童座椅
I'll go grab the car seat.
我去拿尿片包
I'll get the diaper bag.
天啊  那是送披薩的小哥
Oh, God, that's the pizza guy.
艾倫
Um... hey, Alan,
你能把錢給披薩小哥嗎
could you pay the pizza guy?
我在廁所里
I'm in the bathroom!
他怎么做到的
How does he do it?
很感謝你們能來
You know, I-I appreciate you guys coming,
但是你們不必留下來
but you really don't have to stay.
開什么玩笑  我們愿意留下來
Are you kidding? We want to be here.
有言道
You know what they say.
"養一個娃  竭全村的力"
"To raise a child, it takes the Village People."
各位
Hey, guys?
我可能抽得太猛了
I think I may have gotten way too high.
誰能送我去醫院嗎
Can somebody take me to the hospital?
你這不就在醫院嘛
You're in a hospital.
你怎么做到的
How'd you do that?
為什么我們什么聲音都沒聽到
I wonder why we haven't heard anything.
他們把凱西帶去產房  有一個小時了吧
They took Kathy to the delivery room, like, an hour ago.
有時候  嬰兒就是不想出來
Sometimes the baby just doesn't want to come out.
你設身處地想想
I mean, put yourself in its position.
九個月以來
For nine months, you've been floating
你一直沉浸在世界上最好的水床里
in the world's nicest waterbed.
突然有個人打開了活門
Then somebody opens a trap door,
水全部流走了
all the water flows out,
一把鉗子把你鉗住
a set of salad tongs grabs you by the head
把你拽出來
and yanks you out,
然后一個你從未見過的男人
and then some guy you never seen before
開始拍你的屁股
starts slapping you on the ass.
讓我想起我去提華納[墨西哥]的那次旅行
Reminds me of a trip I took to Tijuana once.
看她多可愛啊
Aw, look at how cute that one is.
對啊  奶子也不錯
Yeah, she's got a nice rack, too.
你在看什么呢
What are you looking at?
那個性感的護士  你們在看什么
The hot nurse. What are you looking at?
那個孩子
That baby.
你們真變態
Ugh! You guys are sick.
你們給孩子取名字了嗎
So have you guys decided on a name for the baby yet?
-沒  還沒  -還沒
- Oh, no, not yet. - No.
壓力挺大的
It's such a big responsibility.
我不想給他取一個
I don't want to give him a name
會被其他小孩取笑的名字
that other kids can make fun of.
不幸的是  每一個名字都會被取笑
Well, bad news. Every name can be made fun of.
這不可能
That's not true.
是嗎
Really?
沃頓  你的湖還好嗎
How's your pond, Walden?
沃頓湖位于美國馬薩諸塞州
比較有深度的嘲諷  不過還是挺傷人
It's an intellectual insult, but it still stings.
我中學的時候被人叫做"牙仙拉里"[音似]
I was "Larry the fairy" all through high school.
不是吧  我是"牙仙巴里"
Oh, no way! I was "Barry the fairy."
有人把我的名字艾倫
Somebody noticed that you could rearrange
重新排列后  就變成了
the letters of "Alan," And I became
"小肛門·哈勃"
"Little Anal Harper."
我的名字是"赫伯"[草藥]
My name's "Herb."
大家沒有費勁想哏
Kids skipped the clever puns
就直接把我腦袋塞在馬桶里
and just shoved my head down a toilet.
肯定有很多名字
Well, I'm sure there are plenty of names
是不會被小孩拿來取笑的
that kids can't make jokes about.
兩位哈勃-施密特先生
Mr. and Mr. Harper-Schmidt?
這姓氏也不用擔心被人笑
Yeah, nothing to worry about there.
兩個基佬爹的姓氏用連字符連住而已
Just the hyphenated last name of the two gay dads.
凱西怎么樣了
So how's Kathy?
她很好
She's doing fine.
好的還有你們剛出生的兒子
So is your brand-new baby boy.
天啊  我們有兒子了
Oh, my God, we got a boy!
我可以把杰克返廠換新了
I get a do-over for Jake!
我只用擔心一條雞雞了
I only have to worry about one penis!
我喜歡穿女人內褲
I like to wear women's underwear!
什么
What?
我以為大家是在坦白秘密
I thought we were confessing things.
他來了
There he is.
他鼻子像你  眼睛像艾倫
He's got your nose and Alan's eyes.
拉里  我告訴你了...
Larry, I told you before that...
謝謝  拉里
Thank you, Larry.
看他  多神奇
Look at him. He's so amazing.
想不出現在還有什么能比
I can't think of anything more beautiful
就這么看著他更美好的事了
than what I'm looking at right now.
是啊  說的太對了
Yeah. Mm-hmm. It's true, that's the truth.
但如果那倆俏護士現在開始親熱
But how much more beautiful would it be
是不是會更加美好
if those two nurses just started making out right now?
是啊  說的太對了
Mm-hmm. Oh, yeah.
你還好嗎
How you doing?
挺好的
I'm good.
除了累
Tired.
還有疼
Sore.
看這個小男子漢
Look at this little guy.
能讓我抱抱嗎
Can I hold him?
當然
Uh, sure.
他是世上最美的東西
Oh, he is the cutest thing ever.
來來  擊個掌吧
Hey, hey... high-five.
算你欠我的
You can owe me.
歡迎降生到世界  小家伙
Welcome to the world, little buddy.
我們會有很多歡樂的
We're gonna have so much fun.
一起去玩球
We're gonna go to ball games together
一起去游泳
and go swimming together
一起去泡...泡椒鳳爪
and pick up chick... ens together.
笑一個  快
Smile. Come on.
好
Okay, uh...
看看這照片
Oh, oh, oh. Look at that picture.
全世界最帥的兩個男人
The two most handsome men in the world.
都是我的
And they're both mine.
怎么了
Oh, what's the matter?
可能想找媽媽了
Uh, maybe he wants his mommy.
好的  來媽媽這  小寶貝
Oh, all right, come here, little buddy.
我是說他可能餓了
Uh, I think he might be hungry.
當然了
Oh, of course.
對  沒錯
Oh, yeah, of course.
來  給你
Okay, here.
抱住
There.
我已經開始思念他了
I miss him already.
是啊  愛不釋手
Yeah, it's hard to let him go.
其實是  無法放手
Actually, it's impossible.
非常抱歉
I am so sorry.
等等  剛剛發生什么了
Wait. What, uh... what just happened?
我錯過劇情了嗎
Did I... did I miss something?
她準備留下孩子
She's keeping the baby.
那法學院怎么辦
But what-what about law school?
五年計劃呢
The-the five-year plan?
當我看到這個小家伙之后...
After I saw this little guy...
計劃就變了
the plan changed.
以前我無法想象有他的生活是怎樣的
I mean, before, I couldn't imagine my life with him.
現在我是無法想象沒有他會怎樣
Now I can't imagine it without him.
但...他會是一個出色的父親
But... but he's gonna be a great dad.
-艾倫  -不  他愛他
- Alan... - No, no. H-He loves him.
艾倫  這...
Alan, it's...
好吧  我們直接說點實際的
Okay, let's-let's just approach this practically.
孩子多少錢
Um... how much for the kid?
我有
Uh, I have, uh,
有32美元
I have $32 on me.
我得留3元去超商買晚飯
I'm gonna need three dollars for dinner at AMPM,
剩下的都歸你了
but the rest is yours.
我說真的  我也很難過
Believe me, I feel terrible.
你還難過
You feel terrible?
我們要開著嬰兒安全椅沒人坐的車回家
We're-we're gonna be driving home with an empty car seat.
你知道等我們到家會面對什么嗎
And you know what's waiting for us when we get there?
一間空嬰兒房和一張空嬰兒床
An empty nursery. An empty crib.
一個空...
An empty... uh, uh....
那瑞典東西叫什么來著
What's that Swedish thing
那個能穿在身上的育兒袋
that, uh, that you wear like a pouch,
你可以像袋鼠一樣帶著寶寶
to carry your baby around like a kangaroo?
比約登背帶
Bjorn.
一個空比約登背帶
An empty Bjorn!
一個藍色的空比約登背帶
An empty blue baby Bjorn!
發音難  面對它更難
Hard to say, but even harder to face.
艾倫  別說了
Alan, just... stop.
沒關系
It's okay.
換成是我也不會放棄他的
I wouldn't be able to give him up either,
所以我不會怪你
so I don't blame you.
真的嗎
Really?
我懂  你是他的母親
I get it. You're his mom.
讓你經歷這些事真是非常抱歉
I'm so sorry to put you through all this.
不用抱歉
Don't be sorry.
他很幸運
He's... lucky.
你們都很...幸運
You're both... very lucky.
這就是個圣人
This man is a saint.
他媽的大圣人
A damn saint.
我們走
Let's go.
說再見  艾略特
Say good-bye, Elliot.
-聽著像"挨虐的"  -艾倫
- More like "Smelliot." - Alan.
你還好嗎
You doing okay?
好
Yeah.
再給我看看他的照片吧
Can you show me the picture of him?
行了  你別再給自己找罪受了
Oh, please, don't put yourself through this.
求你了  就再看一次
Come on, just one more time.
好吧
Okay.
給
Here.
看看他
Look at him.
完美的寶貝
He's perfect.
很遺憾這計劃沒有成功
I'm sorry this didn't work out as planned.
他還欠我一個擊掌呢
He still owes me a high-five.
別擔心
Don't worry.
我們會找到孩子的
We'll find our kid.
我知道
I know.
與此同時  你還是我老公
In the meantime, you're still married to me.
沒錯  我還是
Yes, I am.
為什么凱西不把你帶走  孩子留給我呢
Why couldn't Kathy take you and give me the baby?!